[theme music playing]
[laughs]
[Julio] Wherever it is, you're not going.
No, Papa! The lion is envious
of the lioness
because you know that after that meeting,
I'll become even more powerful than you,
and you don't want that. I know that.
[gunshot]
[Arnaldo] Ivy Aguas…
You killed the old Arnaldo.
But now that my memories are back,
I'll make you pay.
[Romulo] Just make sure
you're loyal to Emilia.
Otherwise, you'll get something
far worse than that.
Make sure nothing happens to my daughter.
Diego, we're here.
Don't come in yet.
Something doesn't feel right.
[gunfire]
[Lily] This is a massacre, Agent Salonga!
[gunshots]
-Let's go!
-Mercedes.
Get up! Come on!
[gunshots]
Let's go.
I won't go with you.
If you don't come with me,
you'll die here!
I can help you take Red Dragon down.
[Mercedes] Leave me out
of your crazy schemes.
I trust Red Dragon.
And no matter what you say,
I will never side with you.
[Helena] Get everyone here
because I already know who betrayed me.
There's no turning back now.
We're so close to taking Red Dragon down.
Then you better take this.
A tracking device.
So we always know where you are.
Camia.
Is something wrong?
Damian, Agent Salonga just told us
that Red Dragon is back.
[tense music playing]
[phone chimes]
Damian.
I have to go. I need to report to work.
All of a sudden?
It's nothing. Just a
small emergency. Okay?
Don't worry about it. I'll see you later.
Okay, take care.
Thanks.
Damian.
Be careful, okay?
[soft music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[humming]
[sighs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
THEY'RE TAKING OUR STUFF AWAY.
BUT YOU DON'T NEED TO WORRY.
Boss Diego, it's your turn.
Wait. What's going on here?
Orders from Madam Red Dragon.
You can't do this.
Where is she? Let me talk to her.
The Madam asks, a blindfold or a bullet?
Your call.
[suspenseful music playing]
Lily, does that red dot
represent Diego's location?
Yes, Mom.
Does this mean that's where
Red Dragon's hideout is?
It's possible, Mom.
But we aren't really sure
if she's there, so we can't
just launch an attack.
What matters is…
we can monitor Diego's movements.
[tense music playing]
I'm sure you already recognize my voice.
Yes, I am back.
Now, there's this saying…
that a person's eyes…
are the window to their soul.
And that's why I had you all blindfolded.
So that your souls can't
escape from your bodies.
And I want your worthless
souls to burn along
with your wretched bodies
when I'm done with them!
Now, each and every one of you…
has a reason…
to betray me.
But there can only be one…
Judas here.
Now, if a person's eyes
are the window to their soul…
then my bullets are more than ready…
to give Judas a kiss.
[tense music playing]
[loads gun]
Eeny…
Meeny…
Miny…
Moe. Moe, moe!
[tense music playing]
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe, moe!
Moe!
[tense music playing]
Mama!
Mama, welcome home!
I so missed you.
I came home as soon as you told me
you finally know who betrayed me.
Well, Mama, what I'm saying is true.
I believe you because you're my baby girl.
But that's such a strong accusation.
I'll need proof.
One of the Dragon Ladies took a video
of Lily Cruz saving Mercedes
while the Big Four were being ambushed.
I hope that's enough to prove that…
your lackey's been betraying you.
[tense music playing]
[loud thud]
Ugh!
[heavy breathing]
Go ahead, baby girl.
[tense music playing]
Give the traitor their last kiss.
-[exhales]
-Emilia!
-Do it now!
-I can't do it, Mama.
[sobs] I can't do it, Mama.
I can't…
[tense music playing]
[gunshot]
[Emilia gasps]
[tense music playing]
Ah! [panicked breathing]
Ah!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Emilia whispers] Arnaldo--
[Emilia gasps]
Get rid of that.
[tense music playing]
[Emilia's breath quivers]
[tense music continues playing]
Thank you, Agent Salonga.
Lily, any updates?
My hunch was right, Mom.
Red Dragon is back in the country.
And someone betrayed her.
What about Diego?
[tracker beeps]
[somber music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Mercedes isn't here.
[suspenseful music continues]
[Emilia] Your lackey's been betraying you.
-[gunshot]
-[Emilia gasps]
Mama?
Are you okay?
Yeah. [chuckles]
Emilia, I'm okay.
Don't feel bad. It's her fault.
She's a traitor.
Of course.
[sighs heavily]
[Arnaldo humming]
[chuckling]
Arnaldo… You did great.
Oh, thank you.
Flower for the dead.
Mama, why are you with Arnaldo?
Emilia.
When I was searching for you,
I dug up everything about you.
Including my grandson,
the former mayor of Ardiente.
Arnaldo…
who's also…
a cold-blooded killer.
That's right.
I went to grandma first after
everything came back to me.
So, Mom…
I'm back.
[tense music playing]
[music continues]
Hello, Grandma.
I'm Arnaldo.
Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo.
Former mayor.
Mm-hmm.
[Helena] Favorite grandson…
-…of Julio.
-Mm-hm.
My grandson!
Why are you here?
What are you doing here?
Why am I here?
Aren't you happy to see me?
Am I not welcome here in your lair?
[Helena] But of course!
But you know, the first time I met you,
you were still sick.
Now, I can see that you're back!
I'm back.
My memories have returned.
All the lies they fed me…
All the pain…
And I want revenge.
And the reason why I'm telling you this…
is because I need your help.
[laughs]
Me?
Why me? Why not Julio?
Why not your Mama?
[scoffs]
Well, we all know that
Grandpa's getting old.
He's weak.
And Mom…
Well…
We both love her, but Mom is Mom.
We both love her, but
we know she can't do much.
But you, you're something else.
I'm in awe about everything
you achieved in here.
-Your power.
-Uh-huh…
And I believe you're
the only one who can help me.
No one else.
And I also believe that I can help you.
What do you say?
I promised Arnaldo
I'd make everyone who wronged him pay.
Something that Julio wasn't able to do,
and apparently, you, baby girl,
are not able to do as well.
[scoffs] You can't even finish
off your opponent.
But then, I can't blame you.
Because Julio didn't raise you right.
But we can fix that.
First-time jitters, Mama.
I didn't even know
you couldn't kill up front.
Because I don't get my hands dirty, Mama.
I always ask someone to do it for me.
I don't do my own dirty work.
[Helena] Oh, Emilia.
If you want to succeed in business,
you need to be hands-on.
But don't worry.
Pretty soon, you're going
to get the killer instinct…
-…like your son.
-But I do have…
…a killer instinct, Mama.
So prove it.
[scoffs]
I'm reserving it for someone
named Lily Cruz.
You're not going to be
the one to kill her.
Not even Papa. It's me.
I'm gonna do it myself, Mama.
[tense music playing]
Welcome back.
Thank you.
[suspenseful music playing]
The Madam asks, a blindfold or a bullet?
Your call.
[Red Dragon] I'm sure you
already recognize my voice.
Each and every one of you
has a reason to betray me.
But there can only be one Judas here.
Go ahead, baby girl.
Give the traitor their last kiss.
-Emilia! Do it now!
-I can't do it, Mama.
[gunshots]
[suspenseful music playing]
Jaguar.
Did you notice anything off earlier?
I have a feeling Red Dragon
didn't kill Mercedes.
And it definitely wasn't Emilia.
Someone else was there.
That person killed Mercedes.
Mercedes is dead.
Forget about her.
Just focus on what could happen
now that Red Dragon's back.
What do you mean?
Red Dragon didn't
come back to kill Mercedes
or to have the Big Four's
deaths investigated.
Based on what I've heard…
there will be an important transaction.
Diego, get ready. Red Dragon will need us.
[ominous music playing]
[Damian] I told you everything I
know because I want to help you.
I hope you and Lily use this
to take Red Dragon down.
Lily.
Agent Salonga called.
They found the corpse of
one of Red Dragon's people,
and they can't identify whose body it is.
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[beep]
[Romulo] Okay, I'll call you back later.
Okay.
[Romulo] Get ready.
We have an important
transaction for Red Dragon.
It's with her partners from abroad.
Millions of pesos are at stake here,
along with Red Dragon's reputation
as the number one syndicate
leader in the country.
Is that clear?
That's all. You're dismissed.
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
[beeps]
[Romulo] Get ready.
We have an important
transaction for Red Dragon.
It's with her partners from abroad.
Millions of pesos are at stake here,
along with Red Dragon's reputation
as the number one
syndicate leader in the country.
Is that clear?
[beeps]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[unsettling music playing]
-[camera shutters clicking]
Agent Salonga.
Lily.
We haven't identified the corpse yet, but…
There's a message.
"DON'T BE A TRAITOR LIKE ME." RD
Open it.
Go ahead and open it.
[unsettling music continues playing]
I warned her, Agent Salonga.
I tried to convince her to join my side,
but she refused.
She chose to side with the demon.
I feel sorry for you, Mercedes.
[unsettling music playing]
[music fading]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[tense music playing]
Well, well, well…
This is more I like it.
That's what I've been telling you.
You should dress up appropriately.
See?
It just might even help
bring back your memory.
Yes, you're right. I took your advice.
You told me to wear something appropriate,
and I found this in my room, so I wore it.
-That's good. That's good.
-By the way…
I'm here to return this.
Uh…
It helped me out a lot.
"The truth shall set you free."
That's what you meant, right?
Right. Right, you are.
You're right.
It opened my eyes.
It's fresh in my mind…
The betrayal of Lily Cruz and her friends.
[tense music playing]
Lily Cruz…
whom I knew as Ivy Aguas.
My ex-fiancée.
The wildflower that ruined me!
[loud thud]
Arnaldo. Arnaldo?
-I--
-[heavy breathing]
Arnaldo, are you back?
Is this… Is this the Arnaldo I raised?
The Arnaldo I mentored?
Are you back?!
Arnaldo?
[tense music playing]
[Arnaldo] Mmm!
This is really good.
But to answer your question…
Yes, I'm back.
[guffaws] Damn! You got me going!
-I got you, didn't I? Yes?
-Yes, yes, yes!
-Come here!
-Ah…
-I missed you.
-Whoa!
I missed you.
There's no other greater gift than this!
Arnaldo, my grandson, is back!
From the dead!
You're a bad boy!
-You got me going for a while.
-Well…
[sighs] I missed my
old self. I missed this place.
I missed you. I missed everyone.
I missed this suit.
-Welcome back!
-[Arnaldo sighs]
Wait, wait, wait…
Mm-hmm?
Who else knows that you're back?
Aside from me, who else?
Well, it's just Mom and Grandma.
Whoa!
You got to meet the Red Dragon!
-Oh, yes! Definitely, I did!
-[Julio guffaws]
And you know what? In fact…
she reminds me of you a lot.
You know? Same anger.
Same ruthlessness.
I've got news for you.
Your grandmother is infuriated right now
because I had all her allies killed.
I ordered the killing of the Big Four.
Why not?!
I just took back what they stole from me.
They stole my gambling houses
and my other businesses.
Okay. Let me guess.
You set it up…
in a way that would look like
someone else did it
so they'd kill each other.
-You truly are back!
-I knew it.
-Great minds think alike.
-[Arnaldo guffaws]
And like I told you,
you're the only one who deserves
to be in my place,
in my throne, and of course,
your newfound grandmother's.
-[sighs]
-[Arnaldo chuckles]
Okay, well…
I've got news for you.
Grandma likes me a lot.
-Wow! [guffaws]
-She likes me so much.
In fact…
she gave me lots of information
about her group.
So, here's what I'm gonna do for you.
I'm gonna be your eyes
and ears in their group.
-Okay?
-[snaps fingers]
And then, eventually…
we are gonna take back our business.
Of course.
[Arnaldo] And…
we're even gonna take her business.
-Okay?
-Okay, rightfully so!
[suspenseful music playing]
Diego.
I'm sorry I made you worry.
I'm glad you're safe.
I thought I lost you.
No, I won't let that happen.
-I'll make sure it won't.
-Let's go.
Come with me.
Cut your ties with Red Dragon.
Lily.
This could be our last chance
to take down Red Dragon.
The reason she came back here
is that she has
a huge transaction coming up.
We have to catch her.
A huge transaction?
Then we'll intercept
that transaction, Diego.
Just tell me the time, date, and place…
so we can finally put
a muzzle over her mouth.
Yes, I'll do that.
But I have to go.
They might get more suspicious.
[tense music playing]
Just be patient, Lily.
It won't be long before all this is over.
-I have to go.
-Be careful.
And text me when you get there.
I will.
[tense music playing]
Now…
going back to the group
of Lily Cruz and friends…
As long as they think
that I'm virtuous, or…
I don't know, angelic,
saintly, whatever you call it,
I'll keep an eye on them.
They'll never suspect they've
let a wolf into their midst.
[guffaws]
Oh! I am starting to really love this.
And you…
You are going to give them a taste
of their own bitter medicine.
Exactly!
You know what? It turns
out that being shot…
was a blessing in disguise.
You truly are back.
-And you're so scary.
-[Arnaldo grunts]
You're just like me!
Even more than me. Ha!
-[laughs menacingly]
-[ominous music playing]
Ah!
I love this!
My grandson is back!
Cheers.
Okay, we're all set.
Kindly put the other decorations inside.
Thank you.
[Damian] Camia.
Hey, Damian.
[soft music playing]
Damian?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I got into a car accident earlier.
I thought I wouldn't survive.
Accident?
-Are you hurt, Damian?
-No. I'm fine. I'm all right.
Are you sure?
[Camia sighs]
You should sit down first.
I'll get you something to drink.
Come on, Damian.
[soft music continues playing]
So, you were in Macau?
Yes.
Who brought you there?
People who invested in our organization.
They made sure of my safety
because the fate
of their transactions here
rests in my hands.
You mean to say you have
friends from other countries?
But of course.
When will I meet them, Mama?
Oh. Tsk.
I don't really think
this is the right time.
The situation's too chaotic.
You know, I must admit.
I panicked when Mercedes
had the Big Four killed.
But thanks to you,
we discovered the real traitor.
I know, Mama.
The first time I saw her,
I knew she was a two-faced hag.
And she was the only one
who survived the meeting.
I mean, that's impossible.
So, Emilia,
you need to keep your eyes
peeled at all times.
Lots of people want to steal our position.
All of this will be yours one day.
It has to stay within our family.
I'll make sure of that, Mama.
[sinister music playing]
[Camia] Damian.
Here, drink this.
Thank you.
Come here.
Damian, did anyone else
get hurt in the accident?
Just one person.
But because of that,
I realized life is short.
You can die in a blink of an eye,
and you'll never see
your loved ones again.
That's why if you love someone,
you need to express how you feel,
so you won't have any regrets.
[romantic music playing]
[romantic music continues playing]
[Lily] Mom?
-Mom!
-Yes, Lily?
Mom.
Diego and I met up
and came up with a new plan
to take down Red Dragon.
For now, I need your help
contacting Agent Salonga.
-Follow me inside, okay?
-All right, dear.
I'll be right there.
[tense music swelling]
There will be a big transaction
tomorrow night.
And the shipment must not be delayed
because there's a lot of money involved.
Romulo will be here
to take care of everything.
Why him?
Haven't I proven my competence, Mama?
Especially after I discovered
the traitor in your organization?
It's Romulo who knows
how to deal with shipments like this.
He could be my adviser, Mama.
You have to give me a chance.
How can I learn if you won't give me one?
I did give you a chance, Emilia.
And the Big Four died, remember?
But that won't happen again, Mama,
because the traitor in the group is gone.
[sighs]
All right.
I'm going to give you another chance.
[claps] Yay!
I'll make you proud, Mama.
-Don't disappoint me.
-I won't.
[Helena] All right.
You and Romulo talk about the details.
-Mm-hm.
-I need to rest.
[tense music playing]
And you…
Mercedes 2.0?
You'll really do everything you
can to rise in the ranks, huh?
And what do you mean by that?
Mercedes treated Red Dragon like a mother.
She couldn't have been the traitor.
Correct, that's why she
threw Mama under the bus
because she's jealous.
If you're going to question me,
I could tell Mama that
you have a problem with me.
You know, we can easily replace you
and look for another version of Mercedes.
Well?
Are we good?
Are we?!
Bye!
Scram!
Faster!
[tense music playing]
[scoffs]
[sinister laugh]
[sighs]
Agent Salonga, my contact told me
a shipment will be transported
abroad tomorrow night.
And Red Dragon will oversee
the transaction herself.
Money isn't the only thing at stake here.
Her reputation is, as well.
She needs to show she still
has control over the syndicates.
When will we meet your intel?
[tense music playing]
Once you arrest Red Dragon, and
once she loses all her power.
I'm sorry, Agent Salonga.
I can't reveal my intel's identity.
I have to admit, Miss Cruz,
this isn't how we operate.
But if this is the only way
to catch Red Dragon,
we'll follow your lead.
This is the closest we've gotten to her.
And it's because of your help.
Thank you.
Thank you too, Agent Salonga.
This is our best shot
at catching Red Dragon.
That's why we can't fail.
[suspenseful music swells]
[pensive music playing]
Hey!
You're spacing out again.
Did you have another fight with Jepoy?
What was it this time?
Marlon, Jepoy loves me.
He really does.
Well, there you go.
So, what's with the long face?
I was wrong.
I misunderstood him.
But I'll make it up to him.
[soft music playing]
Anyway, Marlon, I have to go.
[foreboding music playing]
[music continues]
[unsettling music playing]
[Lily gasps, coughs]
Arnaldo--
[Lily breathing raggedly]
-[Lily coughs]
-Yes.
[breathes raggedly, groans]
-Yes, yes…
-Arnaldo! [groans]
Arnaldo!
[coughs, wheezes]
Arnaldo, please!
[groans, coughs]
-[Arnaldo whispering]
-[ragged breathing]
Arnaldo! [coughs]
[Lily groans]
-[Lily breathes raggedly]
-[suspenseful music playing]
[Lily groans]
-[heavy breathing]
-[water running]
[unsettling music playing]
[chuckles]
Lily…
[unsettling music playing]
Uh…
-Lily.
-Arnaldo.
What are you doing here?
Uh…
It's been days since
Diego came to visit me.
Is he there?
No. Diego isn't here.
I don't know where he is.
Maybe he's at work.
Is that so?
Don't you two ever text or call?
Not at all?
No.
Arnaldo, I suggest you go home now.
I'm sure that your brother will visit you.
[unsettling music continues playing]
Uh… I'll open it for you.
[car engine turns over]
Let's go.
[sighs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[sighs] You haven't changed, Lily.
You still smell so good
even though you're rotten to the core.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Noel] It's a wiretapping device.
That way, we can record and listen in
on Red Dragon's transaction.
[Lily] If something doesn't go as planned,
we'll be there right away.
[Helena] Emilia will
eventually lead our group,
so I want you to respect her.
Do you understand?
[Lily] I'll see you at
the finish line, Red Dragon.
And may the best woman win.
[Helena] The one and only
Red Dragon will rise.
I knew it! You're a traitor!
Madam, he's spying on us!
[Noel] Police! Don't move!
[gunshots]
[screams]
Let's move! What are you waiting for?
[suspenseful music playing]
[theme music playing]